Good morning guys, it's Syd, and welcome back.
Yesterday I was trying to think of videos and I was like, what do you guys even want to see from me now?
I would say like one of the top comments was asking for like what I eat in a day videos, just like healthy, easy
recipes, and I'm kind of honored, all right?
I'm like a little flattered that you guys think I'm that much of a chef now.
I like to consider myself a lazy girl chef.
I don't love to be in the kitchen for hours on end.
I just want to make something that's good and healthy, balanced, and just clean without like taking forever.
The past year I've kind of gathered a few recipes of things that I really like so I'm going to share them with you guys.
Over the next few days I'm going to do like a little what I eat.
I get really obsessed with something.
When I find a recipe that I like it's over for the next three months.
I will be eating that on repeat every single day until I hate it like deep in my bones and I never want to eat it again.
The current thing that I'm eating for breakfast, well I'm actually drinking, is my favorite smoothie.
When I tell you guys I think I have the best smoothie recipe, I really mean it.
Let's get the ingredients out.
I freeze my bananas.
So I add about a full banana.
I add a good handful of frozen strawberries.
I add about, I want to say, half a cup of Greek yogurt.
I add some vanilla protein powder.
I love this one by Orgain.
Oh no I forgot I'm out!
I ordered some on Amazon though.
Maybe it's...
oh it's here.
I'm adding two scoops which is like a full serving of this protein powder.
One tablespoon of peanut butter.
I like to add a little bit of vanilla extract.
Quite a good amount of milk.
And then lastly, what I think makes this so good are cacao nibs.
So these add like a little bit of crunch.
I really just like the texture of them.
I remember I went to a smoothie bar once and they did this and that is what inspired me to add them to my own.
So if I have space, I'll add an ice cube.
I'm saying one because these are like ginormous ice cubes.
And that is everything in my smoothie.
So just blend it up.
And
that's it, that's
my smoothie recipe guys.
I really hope one person makes this and tells me just like your honest feedback because I think it's so good.
My boyfriend also really loves this, so sometimes I'll make this for both of us.
As you can see, this makes like two full servings.
You can see little cacao nibs in there.
It just feels like I'm like eating something at the same time, and I just feel so satiated after having this, which for me is the biggest thing.
I don't want to like drink something like this and then be hungry an hour later.
I'm just gonna plan for my day on my laptop.
I like to do this when I have my smoothie.
I'm just like write my whole to-do list in the morning because I get sort of distracted and I need to know exactly what I need to do
for the day.
I'm
back at my favorite coffee shop.
What's happened is I've built a bit of a rapport here.
I have my friends, the baristas.
I have my punch card.
I'm a loyal member.
I don't mess around.
I like their coffee.
So I come here because I like to get out of the house.
You guys know when I work and I do get a lot of questions of people rightfully asking like what are you even doing?
When you say that you like working on your laptop, what does this entail?
It depends.
Sometimes I'm editing a YouTube video or I'm working on a campaign for a brand or something, but I also have a jewelry brand which takes up a
lot of my time.
If anyone out there is also a small business owner, you know how much time goes into it, and it's all fun for me like I doesn't even
feel like I'm really working.
For example, we're having a shoot for our next campaign on Thursday, so I need to plan that with the photographer.
We have the shoot location booked and the model and everything, but there's just like a couple last minute things I need to work on for that.
So that is why I'm here.
I usually camp out here for quite a while, a Good three, four hours.
My recent coffee order has been pretty much the same, an iced vanilla latte with skim milk, but I try to ask for half of the vanilla just
because I'm trying to slowly wean off sugar a little bit, at least just do my best.
I am addicted.
So yeah, I'm just gonna work for a little bit.
I might have a little snack.
I brought my Chomp stick.
So I'm back home now.
I ended up shooting a little campaign with my roommates.
That's why I did my makeup.
If you noticed, one of my friends has a bakery, and she gave this to me.
There is nothing better than fresh sourdough.
Whenever I have a loaf, I just like want to use it up.
By the way, I'm trying to figure out how to make good sourdough.
So if you have any tips, let me know.
I don't have a ton of stuff in my fridge.
I think I need to run to the grocery store, but I have avocado and I have eggs.
So I think I'm just going to throw together some avocado toast.
Pretty simple, but it's going to be amazing because of this bread.
I don't have a toaster for some reason, which poses its inconveniences, but I do have an air
fryer.
I wasn't super hungry, but I did want to have something.
I do think I have also, I'm really making this seem like a science, but I feel like I have perfected my avocado toast.
I have had two different people, and realizing it's like my friend and my mom tell me that they love my avocado toast, so I'll take it.
I'll take what I can get.
I did copy the brand new Melville Cafe on this.
They made their avocado toast with honey.
That to me was something I'd never thought of, and ever since then, I put honey on my avocado toast.
But this time, I did hot honey.
Sometimes I'll do that.
It's fun to switch it up, and of course, you need everything bagel seasoning too.
It's kind of it.
Anyways, I'm head to the
gym.
I made it back home from my workout about an hour ago.
I still haven't changed.
That's kind of disgusting.
I'm honestly probably going to start making dinner soon, but I know it's going to be a process, and I just can't wait.
So I'm going to have a little snack.
I have Chomps all the time, so I was so excited when Chomps asked to work with me.
I have one of these in my purse pretty much at all times now.
They don't have to be refrigerated, and it doesn't take any prep at all.
They're just so easy and quick for me, especially because I'm gone a lot or I'm on the go.
I'm shooting something.
I'm working on Ophelia.
I like these are just so convenient, but they're still, I feel so good eating them.
I love that they have zero grams of sugar and 10 grams of protein.
And they're also great quality because they're grass fed and finished.
They also have Chomplings, which I bring a lot too.
They're like the mini version of this.
These are just my go-to.
I mean, this is my second of the day, so you can probably already tell how much I love them.
I was also so happy because they gave me a code for you guys.
So if you want 15% off your order plus free shipping, you can go to chomps.com slash sid15.
I'll put the link in the description, or I'll also put a QR code like on the screen.
And you can get a little deal.
Grab some Chomps for yourself.
Thanks again to Chomps for working with me.
I am so happy to work with them.
I just like love their stuff.
That is going to hold me over till dinner, so I gonna start cooking.
Me and my roommate, I think, are gonna make little bowls for us.
Olivia and I both have addictive personalities.
We, you know, we get stuck on the same meal.
So one of our like current three rotations that we have pretty much every week are these quinoa chicken bowls.
I've made them a few times on here.
They're just so easy, and I think the key though is having a white sweet potato.
I don't know what about them are so good, especially how much better I think they are than regular sweet potatoes.
But this with some cinnamon and olive oil tossed together, roasted in the oven, is just so good.
Are we adding tzatziki to this?
Yeah, okay, perfect.
Olivia and I have our own duties.
Uh, she's on chicken duty.
Usually I'm on quinoa and sweet potato duty, so it makes it so much easier too when you cook like with your friend or
roommate, because making two quantities of something is just so much easier than like making something for one
person.
We're set, sir.
Hey guys!
Okay.
The best part about this meal is making it with my roommate.
It's so fun.
It's kind of like our time to catch up during the week.
We start by chopping up the one white sweet potato.
Coat it in a good amount of olive oil and cinnamon.
I'm going to put our little recipe in the description, by the way.
While the sweet potatoes are roasting, I start chopping up the zucchini, coat it in olive oil, salt.
I add those in to roast them as well.
Chop up some cherry tomatoes, and then pretty much start assembling everything.
We put the quinoa in, spinach, cherry tomatoes chopped up, avocado, some chicken that we baked in the air fryer, and then our potatoes,
zucchini, and of course tzatziki, which is what makes this so good and kind of just like come together.
All right guys, dinner is ready.
We made our bowls.
It's gonna be amazing, per usual.
It took us a little longer this time.
We made it.
Bumps in the road.
Mm-hmm.
These are our bowls.
We're gonna watch something on Netflix.
Probably like a crime documentary.
Good morning.
I'm making the same smoothie again.
This is the only way that I know how to start my morning now.
I go to bed thinking about waking up to drink this.
That's when you know you're in too deep.
This is not the meal I'm the most proud of.
I was out and about.
I was working.
So I just picked up this chicken wrap with rice, tomato.
Some days are just like this.
It's all about balance.
Hey guys, long time no see.
I've been drinking this Core Power shake.
I do love these, by the way.
So good.
I'm gonna make dinner now.
I have, you know, about three in rotation.
This is probably my number one like consistent go-to over the past couple years, and they're my favorite taco bowls.
They're so good.
So easy.
I can probably finish cooking this in around 25 minutes.
I love my jasmine rice.
So I'm gonna start by boiling this.
It was really devastating at the grocery store because they didn't have pre-chopped onions, which is like the one thing that I really, I'll spend the extra money
on.
I hate chopping onions, and I hate chopping, honestly, a lot of vegetables.
Pre-chop just like makes my life 10 times easier, but you know what, I can live with it.
We're going in.
I don't think these do anything.
Watching this back is a bit painful, like why am I this dramatic?
I start by making my guac.
This is what makes this meal so good, in my opinion.
After I chop up my onion and tomato, I throw them in a bowl with one ripe avocado.
I add fresh lime juice and cilantro.
I know some people think cilantro tastes like soap, which every time I eat it, I think about that.
I just like feel bad for those people.
Obviously I add some salt, and you can kind of do this to taste, you know, add as many tomatoes as you want, onion.
After, I like to cook my ground beef.
I usually get the lean ground beef, and I also add in a packet of taco seasoning.
A little hack, it's so good and so easy.
And then I start to assemble the taco bowl, starting with shredded iceberg lettuce, pretty shredded, of course, if you're lazy like me.
I had the rice, the ground beef, the guac that I made, and some cheese.
You can kind of add just like whatever you would like in your taco bowl.
The more that you make something, the easier it is, because then you know like the shortcuts, you know like what to start first.
So this luckily doesn't take me too long.
Usually I like to have like tortilla chips on the side or something with the guac, but this is just like foolproof.
I feel like you can't really mess up making this.
It's pretty straightforward.
Well, I did burn the rice one time.
We also need to talk about something.
I've been getting hate, okay?
I've been getting a lot of hate, and it's been heavy on my heart.
People are hating on our apartment.
Um, I know.
I know.
There's not a lot of color going on.
Okay, that's why I have the candle.
I think I've just sort of learned that I like more like a minimalist decor like this.
I like the dark walnuts, the creams, the beiges.
And you know what?
If that makes me boring, then so be it.
I just wanted to let you guys know.
I have seen the comments.
And you know what?
I'm sorry.
Maybe for you guys, I'll try to incorporate color somehow.
I have something that I have to edit that was due 40 minutes ago.
So I'm trying to edit this right now.
And then tomorrow morning, I have a shoot for Ophelia.
So I'm also trying to like prep that.
It's already almost 9 p.m. I feel like I have a long night ahead of me, to be honest.
So I got in a good healthy meal.
Good morning, guys.
I know it looks messy in here.
I also am wearing a shirt this morning.
I woke up at like 7 because we're doing a little shoot for Ophelia, my jewelry brand.
It's in Brooklyn, and we like rented a studio.
It's gonna be me, a photographer, the model who actually is my roommate, and my assistant.
So just getting ready for that, which I'm so excited for.
I'm a little bit nervous but mostly excited.
For breakfast, I just wanted to do something really quick because I'm running like a little late.
These are the blueberry maple oats.
I got these at Whole Foods.
You can get them, I think, quite a few places.
My dad and I discovered these together on a trip.
Specifically, this flavor is the best.
There's not too much sugar in this; it's coconut sugar.
I really like them.
Wish me love.
Hey guys, update.
I am done with the shoot.
It went so well.
I am so excited to see the photos.
What I ate today so far was not the best.
I had pastries at the shoot, I had my coffee, and my oatmeal.
I think that's all I had.
So I am very hungry, but I decided to go on a little walk because it's so beautiful.
It's 70 degrees outside.
I feel like as I get older, I appreciate the days that the weather is good so much more than I used to.
Look how beautiful it is, guys.
And then I think I'm going to go out to dinner tonight.
My boyfriend and I are going to go on a little dinner date, so I will keep you updated.
I did forget to
vlog dinner.
I'm sorry, guys.
I feel like the worst YouTuber at these points.
We had such a nice dinner.
It's always nice to like go out every once in a while.
I love some good pasta.
I did want to say I didn't show everything that I ate in the span of these three days.
I just wanted to show the highlights of some of my favorite recipes and try to keep it real too.
You know, sometimes I go out and grab stuff because I'm just in a rush, but I try my best.
Love you guys, and I'll see you in my next video.
And I'll do an outro next time, I promise.
Bye guys!